OURI: Was that a kiss?
OURI: Oh, damn it! I can't concentrate at all!
OURI: Damn it! Damn it! Damn it!
SIGN: I'm the One Who's Gonna Win
OURI: And I need to finish my summer vacation
homework by the day after tomorrow, too!
OURI: A famous morning drama actress.
ACTRESS: Let's go out to eat, Ouri-kun!
OURI: A charismatic top model.
MODEL: Are you free, Ouri-kun?
OURI: Sorry, I'm busy.
ACTRESS/MODEL: Aw...
OURI: No matter how much others came onto me,
OURI: it never resonated
with me at all, and yet...
OURI: What the hell's going on
with my emotions?! Damn it!
UTAGE: This place is closed, too.
UTAGE: There's nowhere open...
OURI: Utage Kinoshita!
OURI: What's she doing here?!
LYRICS: Hey!! It's just like sweeet magic!! Aha!
LYRICS: Hi, it's me!
The one with that killer smile!
LYRICS: Stealing your gaze with a shocking style!
LYRICS: Smooth as ever, I escort you
LYRICS: And this voice, seducing you
LYRICS: Ah, come on, let's dance;
I'm aiming straight for your heart
LYRICS: I am your ace darlin'
LYRICS: Confidence? Yeah, I've got plenty
LYRICS: Please Please
LYRICS: Whisper just to me, call my name
LYRICS: You're too popular,
it drives me crazy and I'm not okay
LYRICS: But I'm sorry, losing's not my thing
LYRICS: Hey, girl
LYRICS: Look this way!
LYRICS: I see your smile, smile, smile,
I wanna make it all mine
LYRICS: Crash, crash, crash,
our special connection shines
LYRICS: Dance, dance,
our world is non-stop groovin'
LYRICS: I'll show you my perfect
A-side, side, side
LYRICS: And my private B-side, side, side;
I'll show you everything
LYRICS: So take my hand and let's roll
LYRICS: Sweet Sweet Sweet magic!!
LYRICS: Sweetie honey Sweetie honey
LYRICS: It's a spell that makes your heart race
LYRICS: We can't go back
LYRICS: You're falling in love with me, c'mon!
LYRICS: Sweetie honey
LYRICS: Sweet Sweet Sweet magic!!
UTAGE: I focused too much on my job and
fan activities during summer vacation
UTAGE: and forgot to do my homework.
UTAGE: I need to finish it by
the day after tomorrow...
UTAGE: "Supernova"!
NARRATOR: The idol group that everyone
has their eyes on right now... F/ACE!
UTAGE: No way! A commercial?!
NARRATOR: Their first on-location trip show
coming soon!
UTAGE: Did I use up all my luck for the day
by running into this today?!
SIGN: A Documentary Program Featuring F/ACE
SIGN: Coming Soon!!
Lyrics: Supernova
Lyrics: Creating a new era beyond imagination
NATSUKI: Jeez! You're way too serious!
NARRATOR: Their latest single is a massive hit!
Lyrics: Supernova
NARRATOR: And we get to see another side of F/ACE!
Lyrics: It's a miracle that we
were born in the same era
Lyrics: So we've got to enjoy it
(Yeah, song song song)
OURI: Good morning.
OURI: I'm sure everyone wants
to see footage of us waking up.
Lyrics: Sing out loud (sing sing sing)
Lyrics: Harmonizing loud and proud
OURI: Don't worry, we made sure
the cameras were rolling.
OURI: T-Tamon-kun's naked?!
Lyrics: Song, song, song
TAMON: Let's sleep together
for just a little longer...
Lyrics: Sing out loud (sing sing sing)
Lyrics: Shining bright as one
OURI: We shouldn't be doing things like this
first thing in the morning, Tamon-kun!
Lyrics: Supernova
SIGN: F/ACE's
SIGN: Super Exciting
SIGN: Summer Vacation
F/ACE: F/ACE's Super Exciting Summer Vacation!
F/ACE: We hope you'll check it out!
UTAGE: I will! I will! I'll absolutely watch it!
UTAGE: Please stream it worldwide
at the same time!
UTAGE: Meaning I need to finish
my homework so I can watch.
UTAGE: If there was some system
where I could deposit 1, 000 yen
SIGN: Internet Banking
SIGN: m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
SIGN: Tamon Fukuhara's
SIGN: Account
SIGN: m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
SIGN: Deposit Total yen
UTAGE: into Tamon-kun's account
every time I finished a problem,
SIGN: Deposit     Utage Kinoshita             1, 000 yen
SIGN: Deposit 1, 000 yen
Deposit     Utage Kinoshita             1, 000 yen
SIGN: Deposit 2, 000 yen
SIGN: Deposit     Utage Kinoshita             1, 000 yen
Deposit     Utage Kinoshita             1, 000 yen
SIGN: Deposit 3, 000 yen
SIGN: Deposit     Utage Kinoshita             1, 000 yen
Deposit     Utage Kinoshita             1, 000 yen
SIGN: Deposit 4, 000 yen
UTAGE: I'd be much more motivated.
SIGN: Deposit     Utage Kinoshita             1, 000 yen
Deposit     Utage Kinoshita             1, 000 yen
SIGN: Deposit 5, 000 yen
SIGN: Deposit     Utage Kinoshita             1, 000 yen
Deposit     Utage Kinoshita             1, 000 yen
SIGN: Deposit 6, 000 yen
SIGN: Deposit     Utage Kinoshita             1, 000 yen
Deposit     Utage Kinoshita             1, 000 yen
SIGN: Deposit 7, 000 yen
SIGN: Deposit     Utage Kinoshita             1, 000 yen
Deposit     Utage Kinoshita             1, 000 yen
SIGN: Deposit 8, 000 yen
UTAGE: Utage Kinoshita, sixteen years old.
SIGN: Deposit     Utage Kinoshita             1, 000 yen
Deposit     Utage Kinoshita             1, 000 yen
SIGN: Deposit 9, 000 yen
SIGN: Deposit     Utage Kinoshita             1, 000 yen
Deposit     Utage Kinoshita             1, 000 yen
SIGN: Deposit 10, 000 yen
SIGN: Deposit     Utage Kinoshita             1, 000 yen
Deposit     Utage Kinoshita             1, 000 yen
SIGN: Deposit 11, 000 yen
SIGN: Deposit 12, 000 yen
SIGN: Fan Activities
UTAGE: I can draw out all my potential for fan
activities, but not really anything else.
SIGN: Fan Activities
UTAGE: No, no!
UTAGE: Even Tamon-kun is working hard
to do both work and school,
SIGN: Menacing
UTAGE: so I need to get a grip!
UTAGE: It'll cost some money,
but I guess I could go to a café.
OURI: If I'm so bothered by not knowing
what her relationship with Tamon is,
OURI: I'll just ask her outright.
UTAGE: Somewhere cheap and quiet would be best.
UTAGE: Oh? Gloomyhara-san?
TAMON: Oh... Hello.
UTAGE: Hello. Today's a lovely day, isn't it?
OURI: What the hell is he doing here?!
UTAGE: Are you heading out somewhere?
TAMON: I went to get the uniforms that
Fujita-san sent to the dry cleaners.
UTAGE: Right. The new school term
starts the day after tomorrow.
UTAGE: You have two uniforms?
TAMON: One is Ouri-kun's.
UTAGE: I see.
UTAGE: Waitaminute! You go to high
school, Gloomyhara-san?!
UTAGE: And to the same school as Ouri-kun?!
TAMON: Oh, yes. Didn't I mention that before?
OURI: Oh, right. I made him go get them.
UTAGE: There's a Tamon-kun that
goes to high school in real life?
UTAGE: Tamon-kun who's a third-year
in high school exists in this world.
UTAGE: How is that possible?
My brain can't process that.
TAMON: I'm right here, though.
TAMON: Though I mostly just do my makeup
classes at night or on my days off,
TAMON: so it doesn't really feel like
a normal high-school life.
TAMON: What are you up to, Kinoshita-san?
UTAGE: Ah, well, I hadn't finished my
summer vacation homework yet.
HOMARE: You take Pochi for a walk, Yamato.
I have a date, and I'm busy!
YAMATO: I have to study, so no.
UTAGE: I can't concentrate at home because
my siblings and dog are too loud.
UTAGE: And both the library
and community center are closed.
SIGN: Closed
UTAGE: So I was looking for a place to study.
TAMON: Hm... Somewhere you can
study quietly for free...
TAMON: I know! You can come over to my place.
UTAGE: There's no way I can step foot into
that sanctuary other than for work.
UTAGE: Oh, I'm sorry!
TAMON: In that case...
TAMON: A table in that park was open.
And it's pretty cool today.
UTAGE: Between those two places,
it'd be the park.
TAMON: Sure.
TAMON: I have to memorize tomorrow's script,
TAMON: so I'll buy some sandwiches and...
KEITO: Hey.
KEITO: What the hell are you two thinking?
UTAGE: Tachibana-san?!
KEITO: Don't just casually go have a picnic.
KEITO: You two need to be more
aware of your surroundings.
KEITO: What are you, grade schoolers?!
SIGN: Facts
KEITO: Come with me.
UTAGE: Huh?
UTAGE: Where are we going?
KEITO: If you have nowhere else
to go, do it here.
SIGN: Frugality Is a Virtue
KEITO: There's nothing distracting here,
so you should be able to concentrate.
UTAGE: I-I guess you're right.
KEITO: Did you eat lunch yet?
UTAGE: Not yet.
SIGN: Save Water
SIGN: Once Open, Three Seconds
KEITO: I have some prepped meals in the fridge,
so you can eat those if you're hungry.
KEITO: Just make sure not to pull the drawer
out more than fifteen centimeters.
KEITO: Once you open the door,
close it within three seconds.
SIGN: Once Open, Three Seconds
KEITO: Also... Tamon, you little...
SIGN: A Journey of
a Thousand Miles
Begins with a Single Step
TAMON: Huh?
KEITO: Did you go outside without
putting on any sunscreen again?!
UTAGE: Please calm down, Tachibana-san! Please!
KEITO: Stop that!
TAMON: I'm wearing a bag over my head, so it's f—
KEITO: No, it's not!
KEITO: Your face is an important product
that prints money!
KEITO: You need to care for it with your life.
KEITO: Don't underestimate UV rays!
Drench your face with lotion!
UTAGE: Huh? They seem closer than before?
KEITO: Also, you look pale.
Have you been sleeping?
TAMON: W-Well, just thinking about
the eight billion intelligent lifeforms
TAMON: wriggling about on Earth
got me really scared suddenly,
TAMON: and before I knew it, it was morning...
KEITO: If you have time to think about
that kind of nonsense, just go to sleep!
UTAGE: Good for you, Tamon-kun.
You've gotten closer to Keito-kun.
KEITO: You can have this.
TAMON: Huh? Dirt?
TAMON: Do you mean I should go
be one with the dirt again?
KEITO: No. They're used coffee grounds.
UTAGE: I'm so happy for you.
TAMON: Are you giving me garbage
because I'm garbage?
KEITO: No. They can help you sleep soundly.
UTAGE: But I've also been worried about him
and watching over him.
KEITO: Just take it!
TAMON: Thank you very much.
UTAGE: If I... If I were born as a guy...
SIGN: Jealousy
UTAGE: and a F/ACE member
I could be that close to him...
SIGN: Jealousy
KEITO: Well, I've got a shoot, so I'm gonna go.
SIGN: Save Energy
SIGN: Today's Savings is
Tomorrow's Happiness
KEITO: Once you're done, just lock up
and give Tamon the key.
UTAGE: Okay! I will.
TAMON: Have a great time...
SIGN: Popular segment on
their official channel
TAMON: shooting Mama Keito's 30-minute Cooking.
KEITO: You don't need to say the name.
UTAGE: U-Um, why are you doing all this for me?
UTAGE: You seemed to really despise fans
as if they killed your parents.
SIGN: Turn off the Lights
KEITO: I saw how hard you worked
during the training camp,
KEITO: and I checked Tamon's apartment.
UTAGE: Huh?
TAMON: He suddenly came over yesterday,
checked my whole apartment, and then left.
UTAGE: Really?
KEITO: It's clear you were supporting him
KEITO: by professionally handling
his household chores.
KEITO: I also know in my head
that fans aren't all insane.
KEITO: So I'm sorry, Kinoshita-san.
KEITO: Bye.
TAMON: Keito-kun has now started to complain
to me more than before the training camp.
UTAGE: That sounds like
your relationship is worse.
TAMON: No. Rather than him suddenly getting
mad at everything that happened
KEITO: Hey!
KEITO: Hey, Tamon!
TAMON: in the past all at once or
quietly clicking his tongue at me,
KEITO: What the hell are you doing, Tamon?!
TAMON: it's less scarier to have him
tell me how he feels.
KEITO: Hey.
KEITO: The hell are you doing?
OURI: Shut up. Don't make me
punch your glasses in.
KEITO: Hmph.
UTAGE: I guess Tachibana-san's the type
that lets everything build up inside.
TAMON: I'm going to do my best so
he doesn't keep everything in.
TAMON: He is our very precious leader of F/ACE.
KEITO: I'm the leader of F/ACE, after all.
UTAGE: Right.
UTAGE: If Tamon-kun says all that,
Keito-kun is a good person.
SIGN: Today's Savings is
Tomorrow's Happiness
UTAGE: Okay, I'm going to start my homework.
FUJITA: Could you not summon me on my day off?
KEITO: Well, I don't want to waste
any money on transportation.
FUJITA: Yes, yes, of course. Okay, let's go.
UTAGE: Is there something on my face?
TAMON: Oh, I'm sorry. I've just never
seen you study before so...
TAMON: It made me realize that you are
actually a high school student.
UTAGE: It's a bit embarrassing
when he points it out like that.
UTAGE: Well... I guess I am usually working
when I'm around you, Gloomyhara-san.
TAMON: Oh, please just think of me as waste
TAMON: that's wearing a garbage bag and
pay me no mind so you can concentrate.
SIGN: Ten Million Yen
SIGN: Data-Driven Management
How High Performers Reset
Condition Management for Professionals
Time Investment Strategies for Management
SIGN: Flash
UTAGE: Tamon-kun is humanity's
greatest treasure!
SIGN: Church of Tamon
TAMON: Tamon-kun is humanity's
greatest treasure!
UTAGE: I'm done with modern lit
and world history!
TAMON: That was fast. I'm impressed.
UTAGE: I do pretty well with literature stuff.
TAMON: Oh, I figured as much.
UTAGE: You did?
TAMON: Whenever you encourage me,
TAMON: you always use so many words
in so many ways, so I figured as much.
SIGN: Tamon-kun is a God
SIGN: World Peace (Sexy & Wild)
SIGN: Rejuvenating Eye candy
SIGN: A Fallen Angel That's
Lost His Wings
SIGN: Tamon-kun
Belongs to
Everyone
UTAGE: Er, um... though I basically use
most of them in an unofficial way...
UTAGE: I'm not very good with
science and math, though.
SIGN: Arithmetic Drills
SIGN: Tamon Fukuhara Kamioshi
UTAGE: Not to mention those got harder
in my second year.
TAMON: I see.
TAMON: At first, I thought you were someone
who could do anything, Kinoshita-san.
UTAGE: What? Really?
TAMON: But... there's no way
someone like that exists, right?
TAMON: You're just working harder than others.
TAMON: That's very admirable.
UTAGE: Th-That's not true!
UTAGE: I'm just doing what I should
because I should.
TAMON: But isn't that pretty hard to do?
TAMON: My handwriting's so bad that I
can't even read the notes I took
SIGN: m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
SIGN: Gloomyhara Font
TAMON: and then I get stuck.
TAMON: Whenever I clip my nails, I bleed...
BG TAMON: Ow...
SIGN: m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
SIGN: Ow...
TAMON: I can't even do what
I'm supposed to be able to do.
UTAGE: Gloomyhara-san...
TAMON: So the fact that you can do
all these things is admirable.
TAMON: You tell me that all
I need to do is exist,
TAMON: but you seem rather hard on yourself.
UTAGE: Well, you're special, Tamon-kun!
UTAGE: Being told that doing the most
trivial things is admirable...
UTAGE: makes me feel tingly inside.
UTAGE: Hm...
TAMON: What's wrong?
UTAGE: I can't seem to figure out this problem...
TAMON: Oh, a trigonometric function problem.
TAMON: Um... Here, I think you... oh right.
UTAGE: He's acting like my senpai...
TAMON: You use sine, cosine, or tangent and...
TAMON: You're right.
TAMON: Your complexion looks much better today.
UTAGE: Now I remembered that...
TAMON: I don't know!
UTAGE: Huh?
TAMON: My brain is smoother than a boiled egg,
TAMON: so there was no way I could actually
remember what I learned a year ago!
TAMON: Please forgive me and my ugly
vanity for being overconfident
TAMON: and trying to act all senpai!
TAMON: I'm sorry that I was nothing more
than a rotten boiled egg!
UTAGE: Tamon-kun is the embodiment
of light born from star fragments!
TAMON: Yes!
OURI: Now's my chance since
I'm in the same grade as that chick...
OURI: I'll teach you everything.
UTAGE: You're so smart and wuvly!
OURI: Yeah, that's what'll happen.
TAMON: Then I'll cheer you on as Hottiehara—
UTAGE: No!
TAMON: But why? I have nothing left to offer
if you don't let me do that.
UTAGE: I keep telling you not to
waste Hottiehara-kun!
TAMON: You keep saying it's a waste,
but it's not a waste to me...
TAMON: You're always so strong
and cool, Kinoshita-san...
TAMON: and the only time you change is
when you're around Hottiehara.
TAMON: Honestly, that's a win for me.
UTAGE: Huh?
UTAGE: Do you like troubling other people?
That's not okay, even if you're Tamon-kun!
TAMON: I do feel... bad about it.
UTAGE: Huh?
TAMON: But... I'm always the one crying
and falling over...
TAMON: and you're always there for me...
TAMON: So... I want to be something to you, too.
TAMON: Not the music video
or the photo version of me.
TAMON: But the me that's
in front of you right now.
UTAGE: The Tamon-kun that's in front of me...
OURI: What the hell am I sneaking around for?
OURI: I just need to march in there,
ask them what I want to know,
OURI: and get it over with!
OURI: What the heck's going on with you two?
UTAGE: We're dating!
OURI: Am I... actually scared to ask?
OURI: My father is a leading actor
that represents Japan.
SIGN: Film Awards Ceremony
SIGN: Toshikazu
Sakaguchi
OURI: It goes without saying,
but he's handsome.
OURI: My mother is a singer
who defined a generation.
OURI: Of course, she's also beautiful.
OURI: Their son is currently
a new idol in the spotlight.
SIGN: Ouri
Sakaguchi
OURI: Everyone would agree that his good
looks rival any national treasure.
OURI: The educational policy of the
elegant Sakaguchi Family
OURI: was a bit different from other households.
OURI DAD: Ouri.
OURI DAD: You inherited our superb genes
and were born into this world.
OURI DAD: Meaning you are a winner amongst
winners just by being born.
OURI (7): Yeah, I know! Everything
goes ridiculously well for me!
OURI DAD: But that's only
if you live a mediocre life.
OURI MOM: You will never be a winner
in the entertainment industry.
OURI (7): Huh?!
OURI DAD: That's because your father...
OURI MOM: ...and mother...
BOTH: ...will continue to be winners!
OURI MOM: Whether you like it or not,
if you stand on the same stage as us,
OURI MOM: you'll be compared to us
and always feel disappointed.
OURI DAD: Having to face a giant obstacle
known as your parents
OURI DAD: is the fate of second-generation talent.
OURI (7): B-But I want to be on TV, too!
OURI DAD: Then you must be ready to surpass
your mother and father!
OURI MOM: Always remember this, Ouri...
SIGN: Family Motto
Strength Is Power
OURI MOM: Strength is power.
OURI: I'm... gonna be the winner here!
OURI: Her relationship with Tamon
doesn't matter!
TAMON: I...
TAMON: Kinoshita-san, I...
UTAGE: Huh?!
TAMON: Ouri-kun?!
OURI: I'll teach you your homework!
TAMON: You kicked down the door
even though it was unlocked?
MUSHROOMS: Gloom, gloom...
OURI: Tamon's in the damn way.
UTAGE: By the way, Gloomyhara-san, weren't
you trying to say something earlier?
TAMON: U-Um...
OURI: It's not important,
so don't worry about it.
UTAGE: I'm talking to Gloomyhara-san.
TAMON: It really isn't important,
so please don't worry about it.
TAMON: Isn't this great, Kinoshita-san?
UTAGE: Huh?
TAMON: Now, you'll be able to
get your homework done.
TAMON: It's great that Ouri-kun showed up.
OURI: Yup, exactly.
I'm sure this buffoon was useless.
TAMON: I'm sorry for being a meaningless
existence and occupying this space.
OURI: I can learn lyrics and choreo in three
minutes and it takes him thirty hours.
MUSHROOMS: Gloom, gloom, gloom...
SIGN: Sting
OURI: He just doesn't have the knack for it.
OURI: Actually, I'm surprised you were
even able to survive this long.
TAMON: I'm sorry that my brain capacity
is less than an ostrich's!
UTAGE: Tamon-kun spends 300 times more time
on hard work than others. I love him.
OURI: Tch.
SIGN: Grrr...
TAMON: Thank you very much, Kinoshita-san.
TAMON: But it's true that
I'm not being very useful...
TAMON: so is there something else
I can do for you?
UTAGE: Then... please just exist.
TAMON: Er... something other than that.
TAMON: Then get me a shine muscat Daifuku
and terrine de marrons!
UTAGE: Wha—
UTAGE: Humanity is not ready for Tamon-kun
to be treated as an errand boy!
OURI: Well, he doesn't have
anything else to do, does he?
TAMON: I'll be back soon. I'll buy some
for you, too, Kinoshita-san!
UTAGE: Wha—
UTAGE: And there he goes...
OURI: Kekeke! Now, no one's in my way.
UTAGE: By the way, are you actually
smart, Sakaguchi-san?
OURI: What's that supposed to mean, huh?!
I clearly look intelligent!
UTAGE: Er, I was just curious...
OURI: That's right. I guess you haven't
seen me get serious in person.
OURI: Academics? Of course, I'm great at it!
SIGN: Work Hard and Practice Frugality
OURI: How else could I play the prince
character if I wasn't cultured?
UTAGE: I-I guess?
OURI: I've spent ten years in showbiz.
SIGN: Co-star
RANDOS: Ouri-chan, you're amazing.
SIGN: Screenwriter
SIGN: Editor
OURI: In order to survive, I needed to be
likable rather than unapproachable.
SIGN: Creator
RANDOS: Genius.
RANDOS: You're truly amazing, Ouri-kun.
SIGN: Critic
Popular Celebrity
SIGN: Producer
OURI: In the end, no one can run away
from what works.
SIGN: Director
RANDOS: You're lovely.
SIGN: Cameraman
SIGN: Director
RANDOS: What a good boy.
SIGN: Scriptwriter
OURI: Today, I'm gonna get her
to look my way for real!
OURI: Utage-san.
OURI: Tamon-kun's great,
but won't I suffice as well?
UTAGE: Ouri-kun's gone into idol mode!
OURI: Oh, I'm sorry for calling you
by your name without asking.
OURI: If you're all right with it,
may I continue calling you Utage-san?
UTAGE: S-Sure.
UTAGE: W-Wow... the background's
all see through...
OURI: I'm so transparent that people say
that there's nothing more transparent
OURI: than the beaches
at Palau or Ouri Sakaguchi!
OURI: I'll make you take this head on
and make you fall for me!
OURI: I'm just getting started!
OURI: Please, have a seat, my princess.
OURI: I'll lend you the notes I wrote up,
so please feel free to use them.
SIGN: Trigonometric Formulas
OURI: You're correct! Well done!
OURI: This is how you do this part...
OURI: Oh! I'm sorry!
OURI: I'll finish you with the reliable
youngest member act.
OURI: It's a little nerve-racking being
here alone together, isn't it?
OURI: But I'll maintain the innocence!
UTAGE: Squee.
OURI: Got 'em!
UTAGE: So this is what Tamon-kun
gets to see all the time...
UTAGE: I'm so moved.
I get to experience being my oshi.
OURI: This hasn't gotten through
to her at all, damn it!
OURI: A normal chick would've
melted into nothing by now!
TAMON: I wonder what Kinoshita-san's
favorite fruit is.
TAMON: What do you like?
SIGN: What do you like?
UTAGE: Tamon-kun!
UTAGE: Tamon-kun! Tamon-kun! Tamon-kun!
SIGN: Fruits Daifuku Fair
TAMON: Maybe I don't know anything
about... Kinoshita-san after all...
TAMON: I'd like...
TAMON: to know more about her.
UTAGE: I should eat soon.
OURI: Why?
OURI: What would he do right now?
UTAGE: Sakaguchi-san?
UTAGE: Huh?
UTAGE: U-Um...
TAMON: I'm back—
UTAGE: G-Gloomyhara-san! This is just...
UTAGE: What exactly is this?!
OURI: I don't know what to do after this.
OURI: What is this aura?
OURI: Murderous intent?!
OURI: Oh, I was just giving her
a little fan service.
OURI: To show her gratitude
for always supporting F/ACE.
UTAGE: Ah...
OURI: Wha—
UTAGE: Wait, is that Darkhara-san?!
TAMON: Kinoshita-san...
TAMON: doesn't like that.
TAMON: Not that I'm an expert, or anything...
but I've messed up before.
OURI: Tch.
UTAGE: What?! You bought every kind?!
TAMON: I'm sorry.
OURI: Is she really not going to look my way?
OURI: Does she really not even...
UTAGE: Sakaguchi-san.
UTAGE: You probably did this because you
don't like me and you were mad...
UTAGE: But I can't approve
of what you did earlier.
UTAGE: You didn't really seem
like yourself, Ouri-kun.
OURI: What?
UTAGE: Tamon-kun has a lot of fans,
but you also have a lot of fans.
UTAGE: So please make sure you
take good care of him...
UTAGE: The pure and sincere idol Ouri-kun
that's loved by everyone.
UTAGE: I mean, you can't be
anyone but yourself, right?
OURI: I thought I only wanted to get her
to look my way because of my pride...
OURI: I thought it was because I didn't
want to lose to him as an idol.
OURI: But that's not it.
UTAGE: You bought so much. Thank you.
TAMON: Is there anything you don't like?
OURI: I...
OURI: I'm in love with...
UTAGE: I love them all! I'll take all of them!
OURI: Utage Kinoshita.
OURI: Damn it.
Credits: \h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hTranslation:
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hSubtitle Timing:
Editing and Typesetting:
Credits: Michelle Tymon
\h\h\hMariana Martinez
Ashley Barboza
Credits: \h\h\h\h\hQuality Control:
Translation Check:
Credits: Alicia Ashby
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hSriram Gurunathan
LYRICS: Uh huh...
LYRICS: Na na na...
LYRICS: I wonder what the world
would look like without you
LYRICS: When I look back,
you've always been by my side
LYRICS: Teaching me what "warmth"
and "happiness" feel like
LYRICS: A speedboat sails across the endless skies
LYRICS: An unwavering course,
a straight shot down the middle
LYRICS: An unbreakable red balloon
found nowhere else
LYRICS: Is this "fate"? Or just a "coincidence"?
LYRICS: Like a wilted flower coming back to life
LYRICS: A light that shines
LYRICS: Through the impossibly dark night
LYRICS: (Light of your soul)
LYRICS: I wanted to grasp it
LYRICS: (I love you so)
LYRICS: So I strived for it
LYRICS: Wanna keep going, wanna keep growing
LYRICS: Bringing our flowers and dreams
into full bloom